I am so happy today because I'm going to
be teaching you guys something new.
[music] And guess what? This thing I'm
going to be teaching you today is
probably one of the easiest strategy you
[music] would ever see on the internet.
And this is a strategy I've been using
for years now. And it has been making me
money. So I thought it's wise to also
expose you guys to it. And I can promise
you that before this video comes to an
[music] end, you will love this strategy
and will want to work with this
strategy. It is not difficult. It is
just something simple for both beginners
and already existing traders. And also
before we jump to [music] the chat, if
you are not part of my Telegram channel
link in the description below, click on
any of the links either the currency
channel, the synthetics channel or the
crypto channel and join us for free
because [music] you guys know I trade
both synthetics currencies or forex and
also crypto. So be sure to click on the
link and join us and also hit on that
subscriber thing if you are yet to do
so. Now like I said I'll be consistent.
I said in one of my previous [music]
videos that I'll be consistent on
YouTube now because I have been off and
all my organisms are on [music] break.
Yes. So I want to bring all the
organisms back. All right. I want to
make all of them active. So, I have to
be consistent. And these days, I'm going
to be giving [music] it to you back to
back to back to back. Without wasting
much time, let's dive straight to the
screen. And I promise you guys, like I
said, you are going to learn something
new today. [music] So, stick with me to
the end of this video.
Okay guys, so this is how the strategy
works. Like [music] I said, it's very
simple. You see forest is such a way
that when you are able to master some
few things you realize it's not
difficult no jagons no terms like there
are no difficult words that you have to
use to be able to make money. It is just
the practicals okay just the practicals
especially when you make the chat your
friend or you always have a chat time.
So now this is pound
JPY on 3 month time frame. Now on three
month time frame I don't do too much. So
what [music] we are going to be doing on
the 3 month time frame is to just mark
our levels. So throughout the video we
are just going to be using levels upon
levels upon levels to make this um to
get our entry [music] on this trade.
Okay. So I've marked my upper level.
I've marked my middle level and I'll
mark another level here. Okay. Now let's
look here also. We have another level
here. You know these levels have already
played out. This ones have already
played out. We are [music] not going to
use it. But because I am teaching you a
strategy, so I have to make sure I teach
you everything that [music] comes with
the strategy. Okay. So let's look at
this place. You see that we have this
level here that has pushed price up. So
this has now become a what? This has now
become a bottom. This [music] has become
a double bottom. We are not even using
double bottom or any uh we are not using
any chart patterns. We are not using any
um [music] indicators. We're just going
to be using levels. So you see how
powerful it is to trade with levels.
Okay. So we have these [music] two that
has pushed price up. We also have these
two. That is why I drew my level here.
We [music] also have these two that has
pushed and I always say that anytime
you see a double bottom you [music]
should know that price want you will
definitely see a reaction you should
know that price want to move upper okay
and anytime [music] you see a double top
you should know that price want to move
lower it is just simple and it's a
secret now we are not even looking at
what is going to happen here because
even if price [music] would break out to
this point um it is not going to be now
so [music] we don't care about this we
don't care about what is happening here
our full concentration let me put
another level here
okay you can see this is [music] also a
double bottom you see I have been using
this strategy for a long time [music]
and I've really made money out of it
okay guys it's just a very simple
strategy okay now let's look at [music]
it so we have this level also here
um this is so you [music] can see that
This double bottoms are pushing price
up, pushing price up, pushing [music]
and even here we have a double bottom
that has push price [music] up. These
are just levels. These are our strong
key levels. These are levels. Okay, I
just want you to understand. So I need
to indicate all the levels for you to to
see how [music] it it works. Is nothing
difficult actually. Now what is holding
this level now is [music] this supply
zone over here. This is the supply zone.
This is what is holding this level. This
supply zone is what is holding this
level. Okay, you can see price has
tapped into it. So are we going to get a
sell to the downside or we will still
get price breaking up and then moving to
this point to fill this gap. Okay, like
I said, for now we don't even care about
that. Our concentration
is [music] to be on the current price
and I thought in one of my videos I said
when you are marking your key zones make
sure you mark it around current price
and that is the [music] exact thing we
are doing here. So let's concentrate on
this part because this place is a supply
zone that's why price is reacting
[music] here. Okay. So now let's
concentrate here. So our concentration
is going to be between here [music] and
here. So here I want to see price
further move up to fill this gap because
this is where the money is lying now.
Okay. So [music] I want to see price
move up to fill this gap. But now this
is 3 month time frame. Are you just
going to enter here? Put our SL and see
price move up. No, we have to move to
[music] the lower time frame to see a
clearer structure and how to enter the
trade. Okay. So let's move to our
monthly time frame. Now this is the
monthly time frame. On the monthly time
frame, you can see almost the same thing
happening on the 3 month time frame. But
here we need to draw another key level.
So we just bring our level here. Look at
this level. You can [music] see this
double. Let me delete this. So you guys
can see it clearer. Today I am happy to
[music] teach you this strategy because
you you don't know how I feel. It is
because it's very easy and if we can all
trade with this strategy, it's going to
be very easy for us. You [music] don't
need to stress drawing all those fishes.
Okay,
I'm sorry, but I'm just making fun. All
right, so [music] this is another level.
All right, let's put this. Let me delete
this and use the circle instead. [music]
So, let's use the this will make it very
simple. So, this is a level. This is
also another level. So, you can see that
this has also pushed price up [music]
and price have been rejecting this zone
for a very long time. And you can
[music] see we have this rejection here.
This big rejection to the upside. This
long rejection to the upside. This pin
bar already telling us a lot. Look at
the pin bar here already telling us a
lot. We had this rejection. Even this
one did not get to the zone. Then we had
another one that rejected [music]
telling us that we want to push higher,
higher, higher. Like I said, we want to
see price get to this zone because this
is again this is [music] where money is
lying and this zone has never been
tested. It was only tested once. So we
want to see price testing it for the
second time. Throughout the video you
can see I'm sorry because this is a very
simple strategy [music]
I want to teach you guys. Okay let's
move to the weekly. So as we move lower
we see a lot. As we move lower we see a
lot. And on the weekly time frame what
are we going to do? We are going to mark
our levels again because I already told
you that [music] price has been
rejecting these zones for a very long
time. Okay. So [music] like I said I
want us to draw our zones at where price
is currently. And now when you look here
realize that we also have this gap that
price came back to fill here. This is
the gap. This is where the money is
lying and price came to fill there. You
know we are saying that we want to see
price do what? We want to see price
break out and then continue moving up up
up. But remember we anytime price get to
a zone where there is a buy we would
want to see a sell. [music] A buy we
want to see a sell. A buy we want to see
a sell. Now on the weekly time frame you
[music] can see price is already moving
up exhaust up exhaust up exhaust. Okay.
So [music] now we are in the exhaustion
phase here. So what are we going to see
again? Are we going to see price move
lower to this point or we want to see
price break out from here to the [music]
upside. For that we don't even care
because this is still a weekly time
frame. Unless of course we want to be
position traders then we can also make
our judgment [music] based on the
candlesticks over here. Okay. So now
let's move lower to [music] the daily
time frame. This is where we are going
to be seeing a lot. And then also on the
1 hour [music] time frame we are going
to see a lot. Okay. Now I always say
[music] let's always concentrate on what
price is doing currently. So we are
going to be concentrating on what price
is doing currently. Okay. Now let's look
at this point. You can [music] see that
this structure is looking very sweet for
continuation to the upside [music] to
tap this zone that we marked on the I
think on the monthly or the weekly time
frame. [music] Okay, this this zone we
mark this zone on the weekly time frame.
So you can see the structure is already
looking nice [music] but this zone is
also preventing price. When you extend
it to the left, you realize that it's a
very strong zone. We have this. We
[music] have this. We have this. Sorry,
let me put it here. We have this.
We also have this.
And we also have this. [music] So price
has been rejecting this. So definitely
we want to see a little reaction from
there. Then we see what price will do
next. Okay. And also like I said, we
want to see price moving up up. Now when
you look here, we had this push, then we
had a drop. Had this push, we had a
[music] drop. We had a push, we had a
drop, we had this push and a little
drop. So does it mean that we want to
see price move higher [music] to the
upper time frame? Yes, we want to see
something like that. But are we going
[music] to buy directly from here? No,
we are not going to buy directly from
here unless we [music] move to the lower
time frame to see what is happening
there. But on the other hand, we also
need to draw our our levels again. So
[music] my next level will now be here.
Okay, this is where my next level will
be. Okay, now when I extend it to the
left, you realize that it is a very
strong zone. So all throughout the the
analysis, you realize that we are just
using [music] zones upon zones upon
zones. Okay. So, let's [music] delete
this quickly. Um, let's delete [music]
this quickly. Okay. So, now let's move
to the 4hour time frame. Remember the
reason why I place this [music] here is
because this is a very strong zone and
this is a daily time frame. Okay.
[music] So, we move to the 4our time
frame. And for me, I usually take my
entries on the 4hour or the 1 hour. The
reason why I use the 4our is the 4 hour
gives me a clearer [music] structure.
That is the power of 4hour time frame. I
can jump directly to 4hour do my
analysis and take my [music] entries
without even moving to the higher time
frame. Okay. If that is if sometime if
I'm trading personally. All right. So
let's [music] move to the 4our time
frame. Now look at the 4hour time frame.
We have a near here. I call [music] this
a near which means price is trying to
get to that zone and got rejected and
push up further. Okay. So now this is
the 4hour time frame. [music] So on the
4hour time frame, let's um adjust our
zone a little. This zone was taken out
over [music] here. This pick was taken
out by by this um this [music] high over
here, this candlestick. Now in one of
the strategies I've been [music] trading
with, usually when there is price this
way, I want to see price come down, move
up to pick out this zone before doing
what? Before dropping. So this zone
would have to be taken out. Okay.
Usually [music] I see this often when um
trading. Okay. So it is one of the
things I've I've recognized I've taken
notice of that usually happens when
trading in either a buy market or a sell
market. So [music] in a sell market I
would want to see something like this.
Okay. price move up [music]
comes back to pick this zone here before
moving further up. Okay, so I would
always want to see something like this.
It usually happens and it [music] is one
of the strategies I already want to talk
about now but I will definitely teach
you um in [music] one of my
one of my lessons or I'll definitely
teach you one of [music]
these this this okay and that is not
what we are doing today. So let's
concentrate on what we are doing today.
I'm just exposing you to some of these
secrets. So you can see price took
[music] it out. Uh what happened? We had
this double top. Okay, we had this
[music] rejections here. Sorry, I said
double top. We had this rejection. This
pin by rejection [music] already giving
us a signal and boom, we had a drop to
the downside. Now what are we going to
do again? As we had this drop, this zone
being taken out, we want to [music] see
price move further to the downside up to
this point to also fill this gap. So we
are going to have something like this.
We want to see price move like this.
Pick out this zone. Okay, before any
other any other um further move [music]
to the upside or break further, come
back for a retest and continue moving to
the downside. But our overall is to see
[music] price move up up up to the zone
on the the zone we mark on the [music]
monthly time frame. Now if we want to
see price sell here before moving up.
This [music] is why every
every time frame you get to you need to
do a fresh analysis because you could
equally see that we we see a buy candle
here. Okay. You see a buy candle. This
zone is rejecting this buy candle.
[music] This zone has rejected this by
candle. Okay to the upside. So obviously
anybody that will see this will
definitely want to buy because price
[music] is also creating a series of
higher higher lows higher high higher
lows higher higher higher lows higher
higher lows. Then we [music] want to see
another higher high forgetting that we
have a zone here that is supposed to be
filled. [music] Okay we have this gap
here. Price left this gap here. So you
need to actually open your eye. You have
this gap here that price need to fill.
Okay. to this point [music] before we
can see any reaction because in between
we can say price [music] is
consolidating. We had this push here
want we see price came down did [music]
not get a push up again. So we want to
see price push down again before further
moving to [music] the upside. All right
because this is a gap. Anybody who knows
how to trade will definitely understand
what I mean by a gap. Especially those
who trade with levels. Okay. Now let's
move to the 4our. This is where the that
is why it's good to always move to the
far because the moment you move there
you see things clearer. Okay. Now this
is our overall we want to see price move
here. But for now we don't care about
this zone because of [music] this demand
zone here that price has rejected this
demand zone. Okay. This is also a gap.
Price has filled a gap [music] and this
is what this is a this is a near miss.
Let me put it there. We have near.
Let me just do it an N. Uh this is a
near miss. This is [music] an N. A near
miss. So price wanted to get to that
point. I know um smart money and SMC
traders we call this inducement [music]
but this is a near miss and you can see
that price entered immediately and we
had this rejection. Price rejected.
[music]
Look at this long pin. This is already
giving us um an idea on what is going to
happen here. Then what [music] again are
we seeing? We have a gap here. You can
see that price drop. This is a gap. We
want to see price come back to fill that
gap. You can see this gap here. Okay.
So, I think that is what is also causing
price to reverse. You can see this gap
here. We want to see price [music] come
back to fill that gap. It is a gap. I
think this happened on weekend or
[music] something. Yeah. So, we want to
see price come back to fill it. Now,
where do we want to take [music] our
profit? If we want to buy from here
before the sell to the downside before
our buy continuation again we want to
see our take we want to take our profit
here at this zone [music]
uh we want to take our profit somewhere
around this zone okay our take if I am
actually
if I am actually or if I still want to
explain further I'll [music] say let's
take our profit here so we can have a
three top so we are going to have One,
two.
So this will be [music] one, this will
be two and this will be three. These are
all levels. So we want to see price come
back to touch the level for the third
time. But if you also listening to me,
sometimes I always say that if you want
to take profit, make sure you give the
profit a briefing space. the way you
give your SL a briefing [music] space.
Make sure you also give your uh take
profit a briefing space. [music] Okay,
so this is what I want to see. All
right, this is what I want to see. I
want my take profit to be here right
after the [music] gap is filled or even
if I am ignoring the gap, I want all
these zones to be taken out. Then my
[music] take profit, I'll give it a
little briefing space. Or I can equally
bring my take profit here and see
[music] what price will do next before
any further sell. Okay, but let's push
our take profit here. Okay, up to this
zone. [music] And when you even extend
it, you realize that is lying on a very
nice. So always give your take profit a
briefing space. The reason is [music]
price might not actually get to the zone
you are looking at. [music] All right.
So that is why I said you should give it
um a briefing space or you can equally
take your first take [music] profit here
and then wait till price get or you can
take your full take profit here because
this is also a very strong zone. It's
just simple. Okay guys, it's very
simple. So here we have our stop [music]
loss and we have our take profit here.
This is 3 is to one [music] week risk
reward. Now let's move to the 1 hour and
see if we can minimize our our zone
[music] again. Okay. So on the 1 hour,
what are we expecting? [music]
We want to see price push down a little
to this zone. [music] Want to see price
push up down a little to fill this um
this um zone here, these spaces here
before moving further [music] to the
upside. So we can still bring our XL a
little below. This will be [music] our
XL very nicely. Then we wait to see what
price will do. So let's see what we have
here. Let's look at something here. You
see very good. This is exactly [music]
what I am expecting. This is exactly
what I am expecting. And you can see it
here. Price came back to fill this one.
When we move to the lower time frame,
you [music] understand why price has to
come back to fail here. And I always say
that in the forest market, we have
buyers and sellers. So anytime [music]
there's a buy, we need sellers. Anytime
there is a sell, we need buyers to make
the price [music] action healthy. Okay.
So now let's look at what is happening
here. So price [music] has to move up up
higher we go higher higher higher
[music] higher higher. Okay. So, we want
to see our takerit triggered nicely.
Okay, let's look at what's happening
here. Oh,
let's [music] see. Okay, let's see
what's happening. Okay, so now
um what happened here was that the zone
was filled nicely over here. You see why
I was saying you need to either take
your profit here or you move higher.
Now, if I were to take my profit here, I
would have been at a a a safer side.
Okay? But now, I have extended it here
and I'll still have taken my profit here
or [music] closed my trade if I see this
rejection. Look at this rejection here.
This is a very long um pin bara already
um telling me [music] that we want to
see price reversing to the downside that
there has [music] been a rejection here.
This candle came back. Let me show you
[music] something. This candlestick here
pushed up without breaking above this
high to tell me price want to move
further up. Then this also [music] has
pushed price down. So we've already seen
the rejection from this point. So on
that [music] same rejection zone, we
also have what? We also have this as our
key level. Okay, look at something here.
We also have a key level. You see when
you draw it to the [music] left, you
realize that this is a very nice key
level. Price has taken out all these
highs. Okay, price has taken out all
these highs to fill [music] this gap.
All right. Now, right after that, what
happened again? You can see our move to
the down side. All right. But let's
first um talk about our takerit here. So
you can see that price move actually
like I said [music] and then now our
takerit has been triggered. Now how do
we now enter a sell [music] right after
seeing this because our price did not
even get to this zone. We just filled
this gap here and then we started
dropping. So how do we actually take our
[music] trades when price has to drop
back to the level we [music] are looking
at? Remember we are looking at price
coming back to hit this level here. So
what do we have to do? How do we have to
enter the trade? [music] Let's look at
that. So now that price has triggered
our TP, how do we now sell from here?
[music] Because remember we said we want
to see a sell to the downside before
price keep moving up. Okay? or we
[music] want to see a sell to the
downside then the price action that to
form here will give us a [music] clue on
what to do. But remember even if we are
selling we still have to be taking
profit in [music] between. So if we sell
from this zone
and remember if we sell uh let me delete
this. If we sell from this zone okay we
need to first take our profit somewhere
here. We need to be taking profits
little by little [music] for us to be at
a safer side. We first take our profit
here because this is also a very [music]
strong level. Then we now come to this
zone for us to always be at a safer side
like I explain here. So right after
seeing this, we want to see what price
action will form there [music] before we
take our cell because we cannot just
jump into selling this trade. What if
you jump in and [music] eventually price
starts moving up again? It means we will
be at a loss. So all the money we made
from here to this point would have been
a wasted time and energy. Okay. So what
are we going to do here? Let's see the
next candlestick that will form right
after this. Um okay. So we have this
candlestick that has formed here. This
is another rejection again on the zone.
Now I want to see things clearer. Like I
said, I take some of my profits [music]
on the I take some of my entries on the
4hour or the 1 hour. Now, aggressive
traders, [music]
okay, would just enter directly after
seeing this rejection and this
rejection. This [music] is a second
rejection on the zone. Okay, so
aggressive traders would have just
entered. Those of us [music] who cannot
wait for confirmation, those of us who
want to make money quickly and we are
too sure or very sure that this zone is
going to hold. We are just going to take
our entry directly and our first take
profit here and our [music] second take
profit at this zone. Okay, that is
definitely what we are going to be
doing. But those of us [music] who trade
conservative, let's or wait for
confirmation. Let's [music] move to the
1 hour and see if we can get a
confirmation. Very good. You can see how
it is looking on the 1 hour. Now I know
people who can also move to the lower
time frame like the um 30 [music]
minutes. So if this is happening on the
1 hour you can see we have 1 2 3 [music]
rejections. Okay. Now um entry entries
are [music]
somehow different from what I am
teaching you now. Okay. [music] I am
only teaching you how to mark your
levels and then use it to take trades.
You realize that on all these analysis
that we've been doing, there's nowhere
we use um a chart pattern or we use a
trend line, we use [music] Fibonacci.
This is pure levels. This is pure
levels. So if [music] you mastered it is
also going to increase your win rate.
Now like I said, I always take my
entries on the 1 hour. So right after
this zone has been has been triggered,
[music] I can equally enter my trade
from here upon closing of this candle. I
can just take my entry from here.
[music]
Then my take profit and my stop loss
here and my takeprofit to the nearest
support or resistance [music] zone. I
can also take my first take profit on
this zone. Like I said, you should open
your eyes and be very smart when trading
on when trading [music] this market.
Okay. So the entries we are going to
have something like this. price will
push up, drop, move again to a certain
level and then continue dropping. Now
[music] if price move to this level,
sometime we want to see um a [music]
structure break. Okay, sometime we want
to see structure [music] break at this
point. Okay, for price to move higher
[music]
again to a certain level. Like I said,
this is also some entries [music] I'll
be teaching you, which I think I've even
taught in some of my videos already. We
want to see price move higher [music]
like this break structure here. Move up
again. Come back for another break here.
Okay, sorry. Move up again. Then we can
now take our entry here. I want to
explain [music] two things at the same
time. Okay, then we can now take our
entries from here. Okay, we cannot take
our entries like this from this zone.
Okay, but if you are waiting for this
kind of structure and it never happened,
you can move to the lower [music] time
frame to look for something like this.
You can move to the lower time [music]
We had a fresh push to the upside. Then
we had [music] a second push after the
break of structure. We have the third
one back to this zone. So we are trading
um
a key zone in a key zone. Okay. So we
first have this this this break here
that has taken out [music] this first
break of structure here sorry [music] to
the downside then price move up. Now if
you are trading and you don't see any
[music] entry here or maybe you've seen
that price just came here without
breaking structure. [music] Okay, we see
that price just came in between here
without [music] breaking any structure.
What do you have to do? You have to wait
for this move again to do what? [music]
To push further down like this. And now
break a structure. Okay, so we want to
see it twice. And now break a structure
[music] here. Okay, and then move up.
Move up like this. Okay, again before
the drop. So this is going to be our
main confirmation [music] if we don't
see any confirmation here or if we don't
want to enter aggressively. So this is
not going to be our main
um sorry this should be here. This is
not going to be our main confirmation.
So if we see here what are we [music]
going to do? We just bring our short
position too and then boom we enter a
cell right from this zone. Okay. So this
is what we would want to see. If we
don't get our face first break of
structure here, [music]
then we have to wait for the second
break of structure. [music]
Price pulled up and then we take our
entry right from there. Okay. So let's
look at what price [music] has to do
here. So now let's go to 30 minutes time
frame [music]
and then I'll show you what I mean by
you waiting for [music] price to get to
that zone. All right, let's move to
the
lower
time frame.
Okay.
Um
let's delete this [music] quickly
and be patient until I finish teaching.
You need to understand some few things.
Okay.
Now this is the 30 minutes. Okay. When
you look at this side [music] I cannot
properly see a break of structure here.
Okay. I cannot properly see a break of
structure. So our first entry on the
4hour the 1 hour was aggressive. Then
the second one I cannot see a proper
break of structure. [music] So I price
moved here. Okay. Then others will also
take their entry directly from [music]
here. Maybe they will move lower to see
if price has really broken structure.
But for me I cannot move any more lower.
Even here [music] I can still not see
any break of structure. Price has not
broken any structure here. [music]
There's no change in in in price here. I
cannot see anything. Even though we
already have the move to the upside, I
can still not see anything. So I have to
wait till I get a very good confirmation
because [music] remember we say we want
to see price moving to the upside
[music] which means that we need to be
very careful when trading so we can
actually get what we we want. Okay.
[music] So let's see what is happening
here. Now let's look at this point. You
realize that finally we had price doing
what? Price breaking from here. Okay.
[music] You can see this zone that price
has now broken this zone nicely here.
You can now see that price has broken
nicely here. Okay. Now to me because I
already know what I'm doing. What will I
do? I'll just wait for this mini zone.
I'll just wait for a tap up to that mini
zone. Then I cannot take my entry.
[music] So that will be a pullback or a
kiss. Look at what is happening here.
This is the 30 minutes time frame. You
can see price now broke up and then we
have what a keys back to that same zone.
This is the keys here. So immediately
[music] I see this because on under
normal circumstances I was waiting for
price to actually come up a little but
[music] price is not get there.
Immediately it touches the zone. Okay.
Immediately it touches this zone. We've
already seen a pull back. Now the moment
I see this because price has already
broken [music] my mini zone. The moment
I see this I am not wasting too much
time. Just going to pack everything.
Okay, I'm just going to [music] pack out
everything from the market. I'm not
going to waste any time again, guys.
Don't need to waste time. Need to just
move on. Okay, need to just move on.
Make money. That's the most important
thing. So, boom. Take my first take
profit here. Okay, here is my [music]
first take profit right here. And my
second take profit to this zone.
Remember this is where we want to see
our second take profit. But first
[music] let's take our first take profit
here. So you can see that this analysis
is one of the easiest. I I [music] am
trying my best to explain everything
into details guys. So you all can
understand what I [music] am trying to
teach. Okay. So now look this is it.
Look at this. [music] We had this break
and we had this price moved up down
[music] to hit our take profit. Okay,
look at something here. Now remember our
um so we've already taken some profit.
Remember [music] our our overall is to
see price gets here. So once you take
some profit, you can now allow the rest
to run or you can equally take um
partials or even
break even. Yeah, something like that.
You can just break even. So we [music]
want to see price directly at our
takerit. Okay. So now this is where our
takerit is. The reason why it's looking
very huge here is because we move to the
lower time frame. Let's move to the um
[music] higher time frame which is the
4hour. You see that it is a normal
thing. This is looking so nice. You see
huge candle huge candles [music] huge
candles telling us that the sellers are
still taking charge of them. So this is
where we are going to be looking for
another buys opportunity because
remember this is a very
strong [music] level. So you you'll see
that in all the in all the analysis I've
been doing was this levels to [music]
levels to levels to levels. Okay, it's
not that complicated.
>> [music]
>> Once you know how to find an entry, once
you know how to mark your level, once
you know how to put um two or three
confluencies together, you are good to
go. So, this is just a simple [music]
strategy I wanted to introduce you guys
to. And [music] you see, um if it is
your first time, you might not really
get it easy because you really have to
find where the levels are. Okay? [music]
But this is not the first video I'm
going to be doing about how to trade
[music] with levels or how to trade with
zones like this. I'm going to be doing
more um uh I'm [music] going to be doing
more videos on how to actually trade
like this. So by the time you have
finished [music] watching like three,
four or five videos, you'll become used
or it will become very easy and be at
your fingertips. And I know most of you
are definitely going to stop your
trading your [music] strategy and trade
like this because this this looks
simple. Okay, like I said, all you need
to do is to be able to mark the levels
very well, know where [music] price want
to go. And anytime you move from one
time frame to another, try to draw a new
levels. Even if you are drawing the
levels [music] and you you you didn't
get the levels right from the beginning,
at least the closest ones or the closer
ones should be taken into consideration.
Okay? Then now you not look for
confluences. You not look for entries.
[music] You not look for candlestick
patterns. You not look for consecutive
conservative entry uh uh h strategies.
And then you can now boldly enter your
trade and make money. You don't need to
stress most of the charts or most of the
signals I drop on [music] synthetic
because synthetics respect structure a
lot. Okay. So most of the signals I drop
on synthetics. I trade with this
strategy. Okay. [music] I can trade with
um the SMC or the ICT strategy which I'm
also going to be teaching you on my
channel. And I also have different
strategies I I can trade with. Okay. But
you see this particular strategy that's
what I use in trading synthetic because
synthetic respect structures and it is
very simple and sometimes even on the
currency I use it to trade. So it depend
on what the chart is telling me depend
on what market I am trading and what the
market is trading and I have been using
this strategy for a very long time and
consistently [music]
I've been making profit. So this has
brought us to the end of today's video.
Thank you for watching
and I hope you've also learned something
new. Okay, now hit on that likes button.
I want to see your [music] thumbs on
that likes button and also if you've not
subscribed just hit on that subscribe
button and leave a comment in the
comment section. I want you this time I
want you to leave um topic [music] you
would want me to teach on my channel. So
I want you to leave the topics in the
comment [music] section. and I'll see
you in the next video and trade safe.
[music]
>> [music]